tell a business here is so there my new partner here
tell a quick story
soon you tell me i'm clumsy
I am not
nobody
sleeps me over just to feel good
clumsy I am not
nobody
sleeps me over just to feel
goes around several times
will take 1 day
no excuse everyone
Bora or Charlie Brown
he comes in with a proposal that is different from a
normal product
which is a product that has history
has bringing
he agreed to put Charlie Brown on his operation
guaranteeing sixty thousand brownies
already in his wake he has
what is its manufacturing capacity
ten days he gets a hundred thousand brownies
it has the possibility to fold yes
and this guarantees within an existing operation
putting six reais each brownies
also has online operation
gives three hundred and sixty thousand turnover a month
updating 4,320,000 per year
15% liquid image
that's not bad for me fuck
I want to see if it makes sense to you
offering no entry cost
ten percent of Charlie Brown
any objective with you in the operation
channels tá
consult a media
Forecuted
acceleration bar
a percentage
I accelerate the sales projection
and the number that makes sense
if for twenty percent
that there you remain with more authority
you get fifty percent
they thirty and i twenty
already has projection in what you told me
of four million
just because you already have an open channel
clay that I'm taking from the channel yes
including large markets
glands
mini markets
convenience posts
cellar all these places are potential for
Charlie Brown sale
triples
what are you talking about again
minimally
I don't want to enter
take what you will gain
I want to enter
to add up and you earn more and I earn more
I'll call you
I think a good strategy is
I fall
I won't be one hundred percent
dick face
I will be fifty
one hundred percent is you
and then you have to tell me no
if i make sense
that's it
I usually say that God invented the coincidences
to remain anonymous
so all of this here for sure is one thing
ed
called by god
the fact of us
having known each other in an atypical situation
and now becoming a member
because good things will come
e hope that
now from Cara
congratulations hand
I will be very in that